Risley, Robert, Papers /4154
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert Risley Papers
1976-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Risley, Robert B.
/4154
26 cubic feet
26 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
3108568
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 04, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Robert F. Risley (March 28, 1922-January 20, 1994)
Robert Risley who spent most of his working life at Cornell, grew up in Horseheads, New York and graduated high
school in 1940.
Graduating from Union College in 1948, Bob came to Cornell's newly established School of Industrial and Labor Relations where he earned the M.S. degree in 1949 and the Ph.D. degree in 1953. While still working on the degree, Bob was administrative assistant to ILR Dean Martin P. Catherwood. He also served a year as consultant to the President of the State University of New York on administrative organization and personnel policy. His dissertation dealt with faculty personnel policies.
Bob Risley was appointed to the ILR faculty in 1953 and a year later was promoted to the rank of Associate
Professor. In 1959, he became Acting Dean of the School pending selection of a new dean. This was an assignment
he was to take on again on two other occasions, in 1963 and in 1971. In 1960 and 1961, Dean Catherwood, who
had become Industrial Commissioner for New York State, persuaded Bob to take a leave of absence to assist him
as Deputy Commissioner for New York City. From 1963 to 1970, Bob was Associate Dean for Extension and
Public Service. From 1971 to 1974, he served in Day Hall as University Vice Provost. All of these assignments
called on Bob Risley's special talent and sensibility in working with varied persons and interest groups whether
he was dealing with governmental bureaucrats, legislators, labor or business people, or university employees. He
accomplished these purposes, less by rhetorical skill, than by dint of a keen, perceptive and creative intelligence.
He was a continuing source of fresh, imaginative ideas to those with whom he worked, and in turn he encouraged others to perform at their best.
In his various roles at Cornell, Bob was active in the affairs of the ILR Alumni Association. It was his idea to
establish an annual award to honor a distinguished graduate of the School who has demonstrated exceptional
professional accomplishment in the field of industrial and labor relations. Over the years, the Judge William B.
Groat Award has become highly prized. Fittingly, Bob himself was the 1989 recipient of the award.
From his graduate student days on, Helen and Bob Risley lived in Candor where they became central figures in the
life of the village. Here they raised their two sons, Robert, Jr. and Thomas. Helen was a popular high school teacher.
For over 25 years, Bob was active in public education as a member and president of the Candor School Board and
also with the Tompkins-Seneca-Tioga Board of Cooperative Educational Services, including time as its president.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /3012: Alice Cook Papers /3035: Eric Polisar Papers /4053m: ILR School Report on the Off-Campus Labor Relations Credit Programs /4078 AV: ILR School 40th Anniversary Audio cassettes 6038 P: Photographs Archival Collection 6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
Risley, Robert F. (Robert Francis), 1922-; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3108568
- ILR 260 - Fall 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 262 Field Study Trip N.Y.C., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Class Trip N.Y.C. Oct. 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- N.Y.C. Field Trip (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR 260 - Fall 1976 Grades (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILR-260 - Fall '75, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ILR-260 Fall '75 Urban Problems and Manpower Problems, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ILR-696 - Personnel Admin. Gov't. Regulation Fall 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Albany '78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- For 260, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILR 260 - Fall 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Risley's 260 Fall 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1974 Progress Report (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Spring 1974 Estate Legislators (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ILR 368 - Spr. 74, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Prof. Risley (Binder), 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound, Binder
- Posner Conference, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Round Table Conference on Research, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cornell Mgmt. Conferences, 1952-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Memorandum's + Misc., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- American Society for Personnel Administration, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ASPA, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Israel Conference, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Israel Conference, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Israel Conf., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Sloan Foundation Grant 1975 NYS Eco. Conf. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Albany '77, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Johnson, Lisa Sp. 89, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Zankowsi, John, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- SRBA, Michael A., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 'Clean Language' (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Affirmative Action Guide for Employment Opportunity, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Building Proposal - NYSSILR (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Bound
- Revised Building Proposal - NYSSILR, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Affirmative Action Guide for Equal Employment Opportunity, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- ILR Extension Programming for Companies: An Interview Survey (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Basic Labor Law, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Host Packet, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 'Here are the Two Sets from Ned Rosen', 1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Gilbert, Richard Ardwyn Binding, 1969-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Emblidge - McCullagh, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- NYSSILR, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- ISCOL TEISTAR, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lednicer, Oliver Kruysman, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Course Outline, Reserve Class Roster, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- ILR 460 Term Paper Proposals, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Class Handouts, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ILR 460 Evaluations, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- ILR 460 Oral Reports, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Class Notes and Assignments, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Articles of Interest Handouts, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Course Outline, Revision TA Info, Student Info Forms, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Larry Williams Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Lee Stokes Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Chuck Gorski Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Ed Gonzalez Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- John Boudreau Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Karin Ash Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- ILR 260 - Course Outline, Reserve, Class List - Sp. '89, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- McMurtrie, Cindy 260 TA Sp '89, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Gesoff, Rochelle TA Sp, '89, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- ILR 460 Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- ILR 260 Xtra Handouts Spring 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- ISCO1 Telstar, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Lednicer, Oliver Kruysman Inc., 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Gilbert, Richard Ardwyn Binding, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Emblidge - McCullagh, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Billings Standard, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Findelstein, Mark 2/5/90, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- ILR 260 Correspondence Sp. '89, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Anne Farley Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Stanford Seed Co. - A Flourishing Business (Box 3, Folder 33)
- "S.J. McCullagh Inc.", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Cornell University ILR PR 460, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Telstar Communication Ken Iscol, President, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Kruysman-Redweld, Inc., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Stanford Seed Co. (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Collective Negotiations in the Public Sector (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Contract Negotiation in Private Industry: Preparation and Practice (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Union Administration By Objectives by Al Nash, Instructor NYSSILR (Box 4, Folder 3)
- The Visible Union in Time of Stress (Box 4, Folder 4)
- A Study of the Probable Economic and Social Effects of Constructing and Operating the Bell Nuclear Power Station in Tompkins County, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Preliminary Draft Report, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Summary Report of Illumination Products Industry Study (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Report of Out of State Domestics (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Techniques of Managerial Development 4th Annual Conf. of Training Directors July 1950 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- The Frequency Distribution and its Graphical Representation by Philip J. McCarthy (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Manual of Administrative Practices and Procedures (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Sumerbank Executive Training Program Project Manager's Report, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- The New York Disability Benefits Law James C. Vadakin Feb. 1952 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Relation of Vocational Education in the High Schools to the Programs of the Institutes Lynn A. Emerson (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Representatives of Government, Management, and Labor who Attended Research Conference, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- The American Soldier, Vol. 4 A Review by Philip J. McCarthy (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Principal Components of Scale Analysis - A Critical Review by Philip J. McCarthy (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Introduction to Statistical Reasoning Philip J. McCarthy September 1950 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Digest of Conference Discussions: Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics N.A. Tolles September 3-9, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Preliminary Digest of conference Discussions Second Annual Conference on the Reaching of Labor Economics August 26, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Teaching of Industrial Relations and Labor Economics OSU June 13-15, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Teaching of Labor Economics 4th Annual Conferences September 7-9, 1950 N. Arnold Telles (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Teaching of Labor Economics 3rd Annual Conference September12-14, 1949 N. Arnold Tolles (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics Preliminary Digest Part 2, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics Preliminary Digest Part 1 1948 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- State University of New York Report of Committee on Personnel Policies, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Work Sheet for Planning an Overall Training Program J. Brophy Spring '53, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Toward Mutual Understanding (Movie Script) J.J. Jehring January, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Labor--Management and Economic Growth, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Elections in Rural New York C.A. Bratton and E.A. Lutz March 1948 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Report of Committee on Personnel Policies Tentative Draft Sept. 22, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Buffalo-Niagara Manpower Stabilization Plan Appendix A (Box 4, Folder 32)
- "Informative Meetings - The Whys and Wherefores" Dr. W. C. Schwarzbeck (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Report of the Dean of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Manpower, Wages and Labor Relations in World War 2 Compiled by Ghent, Waltcher, and Bael, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Role Playing in Action- Chris Argyris, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Rochester Transit Work Stoppage May 1-23, 1952 Rochester, New York (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Buffalo-Niagara Cont. Appendix G, 1940-1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Longshore Industry Work Stoppage October - November, 1951 - Port of New York (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Board of Directors ASTD, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- ?Board of Directors ASTD, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- ASTD, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- ASTD, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- ASTD, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Bob Risley, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Chapter Administration Manual - ASTD, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Post Card (2nd Follow up) Request for 2nd Questionnaire, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Special letters that Accompanied Original Questionnaire, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Requested 2nd, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Chain Store Refusal File, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Chains to be Followed Up, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Small Stores, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Large-Store, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Correspondence with Stores in Secrecy Special Problems + Questions, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Promises Returns, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Correspondence with Large Stores for Intensive Final Follow Up, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Promise - + In, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Small Store, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Draft 1955 Retail Personnel Study (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Sample (Follow-Up Letters Thank-You Letters), 1955 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Special Correspondence. - Response In., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Requests for 2nd Questionnaires, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Large Store, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- A Survey of Small Business Needs, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Correspondence with pre-test group, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Relationship Between Size of Firm, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- New York State Large Store Questionnaire Straight Runs (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Large Store Questionnaire Results Union vs. Non-Union Stores, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Retail Study Prof. R. Risley (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Foltman I.L.R. Stored 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Prof. Jensen I.L.R. 810 Stored 1962 1 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Professor I.L.R. Stored Nov. 1962 2 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Professor I.L.R. Stored Nov. 1962 3 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- ILR R. Risley Retail Store Project (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Risley Min. Wage Study 3 of 3 Boxes (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Risley Min. Wage Study 2 of 3 Boxes (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Risley Min. Wage Study 1 of 3 Boxes (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Risley Min. Wage Study 1 of 2 Boxes (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Risley Min. Wage Study 2 of 2 Boxes (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Chicopee Orientation Program, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Savings Bank Meeting N.Y.C. - Mar. 26, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Cal - Savings Bk. Conf. - R.F. Risley's Session, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Cortland Savings Bank Study, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Cortland Saving Bank Study, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Cortland Savings Bank Study, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Preparing a Guaranteed Employment Plan, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- The Guaranteed Wage, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Job Safety Analysis - Safety Inspector, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- ILR, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Training Specialist Service (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Misc., 1956 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Misc., 1956 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Building Employee Morale, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Developing and Conducting Industrial Training Programs, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- ILRPR 460 Small Business Course Reading Cards, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Rolodex (Box 12, Folder 2)
  (Rolodex Index)
- Names, Addresses (Boxed) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Boxed
- PSNL Exercise 1 Risley 460 (VHS) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  VHS
- Interview with Donald Sleinan Director - Civil Rights, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Video Tape
- Risley 4/27/88, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Risley 4/27/88 9-10 AM, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Mark Foundation 9/4/88, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- ILR 362 Term Project - Affirm. Action - Interview with Jack Cartwright (Cassette) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Cassette
- ILR 362 Term Project - Affirm. Action - Interview with Louis Cunningham (Cassette), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- ILR 362 Term Project - Affirm. Action - Interview with John "Jim" Cartwright (Cassette) (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Total 92 Minutes - Low Noise (Cassette) (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Telstar Communication Risley 460 Video Tape (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Stanford Seed Company - A Case Study (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Ardwyn Binding Case Risley 460 Video Tape (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Ardwyn Binding Products Case Study, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- 460 Spring 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Case Two (Box 13, Folder 15)
- McCullagh Case Study - Case 5 - ILR 460 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- ILR 460 Case 1 Video (Box 13, Folder 17)
- ILR 460 Case 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- ILR 460 Case 4 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Stanford Seed Company (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Kruysman Class Present (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Edited Risley VHS (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Kruysman-Redweld Case Study 2/90, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- (Untitled Cassette) (Box 13, Folder 24)
- (Untitled Cassette) (Box 13, Folder 25)
- 11/16/88 Risley, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Warm Elbridge - Fall '88, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Robert R. Julian - Risley (Box 13, Folder 28)
- August 6, Toms River, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Toms River, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- N. Jersey, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Toms River Overtime Work Case, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Toms River - Case 1, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Toms River, Mediation Case April 22, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Case between Taylor Chevy. Corp. and U.A.W. Local No. 1034, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Geneva Fact-Finding, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Fairbanks vs. Local 324 UE, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Arbitration Case: Local 852 General Warehousemen's' and LeComte and Co., Inc., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Feb. 25, 1965 - Arbitration Case Rockefeller Center, Inc., Versus Maintenance Div. Bldg. and Const. Trades Council of N.Y. (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Arbitration Case at Finger Lakes Race Track July 25, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Hobart College Arbitration - (Blake Coben Kaiser) Geneva, N.Y., 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- April 2 - Elizabeth, NJ - April 14 Mediation Case, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Letters and/or Memorandums to be Checked, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Arbitration - Standard Furniture Co. nd Local #3115 - Wednesday, 1965 Heckimer (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Arbitration Case, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Dec. 21 - N.Y. City - Arbitration, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Dispute between Taylor Chevy Corp. and U.A.W. Local No. 1034 Rochester, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- ILR 460 Spr. 1990 Part 1 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Newspaper Clippings - The Wall Street Journal, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- WSJ News Clippings, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Clippings from Wall Street Journal, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Newspaper Clipping, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- BES Seminar Nov, 6. 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- NUEA-Speech July 22, 1968 Miami Beach, Florida (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Speech Volunteer Agency- 1/8/69, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Speech to American Institute of Steel Construction - May, 1. '69, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Manpower Trends and problems Conference So. Fallsburg, N.Y. Oct. 6, '70- Lois Gray, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Training in Transition March, 7. 1968 - ASTD (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Extension Activities of Industrial Relations Centers - May 17, 1968 IIRA, Chicago, Illinois (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Speech Owego Kiwanis Club 2/17/66, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Speech Owego Rotary Club 3/1/66, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Economic Growth in Tioga County and Role of Bankers, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Seminar on Labor Relations in Sate Government Speech, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Regents Symposium on Continuing Education October 25, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Ag-Extension Talk- March 4, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- 2) Governmental Relations Actions Bulletin, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Mgmt.. Institute at Rockland Community College, Inc., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- 4) ILR Newsletter, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- 5) AEA Washington Newsletter, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- 6) Public Employee Relations, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- 7) County Officer Training Center Project, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- (ILTP) International Labor Training Program, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Report on the International Labor Training Program N.Y.S.S.I.L.R. Cornell University - Maggie Blough, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- (ITLP - Applicants - 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- ITLP - Advisory Board, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- (ILTP) - Budget, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- ILTP - Curriculum, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ILTP - Internships, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Bales, Mitzi - (ILTP) Applicant, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Goodwyn, Jack E. - ITLP Applicant, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Knight, Donald - ITLP Applicant, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Lyons, Francis J. - ITLP Applicant, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Mackin, Ed - ILTP Applicant, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Myrtue, Martin - ITLP Applicant, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Savolainen, Bill ILTP - Applicant, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Valenciana, Cliff - ILTP Applicant, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- ITLP - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- ILTP - Secretariats, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- ILTP - Policies and Procedures, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- RD - European Trip - ITLP, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- ITLP -1962- Memo of Understanding (Box 16, Folder 19)
- ITLP -1962- Report 5/8/62 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- ITLP -1962- List of Participant (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Blyler, James - ITLP Drop-Out, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Miller, Thomas V. - ILTP Intern, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Smith, Ronald H. - ILTP Intern, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Szarejko, John - ILTP Intern, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Thalmayer, John C. - ITLP Intern, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Townsend, Walter L. - ITLP Intern, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Wilson, Edwin P. - ITLP Intern, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- ITLP - Program Applicants 61-62, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- ITLP - Applicants, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- ITC Correspondence 1966-7, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- ITC Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- ITC Correspondence 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- ITC Correspondence 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- ASTD Correspondence 1966-7, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- ASTD Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Petition of the Erie Club Inc., - The City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Petition of the Erie Club, Inc., - The City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- City of Buffalo - The Buffalo Professional Firefighters Association, Inc., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Petition of the Erie Club., - The City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- PERB Board (Public Employment Relations Board), 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Memos, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Buffalo Professional Firefighters Association, Inc., 1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Petition of Local 907 -and- The City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Petition of Local 907 -and- The City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- The City of Buffalo -and- The Buffalo Professional Firefighters Association, Inc., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Petition of Local 907 -and- The City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Petition of The Erie Club -and- The City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Task Force Report: The Police, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Task Force Report: The Police, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Presentation of Erie Club Inc. Buffalo Police Association, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Erie Club Inc. Buffalo Police Association, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Buffalo Professional Firefighters Association, Inc., 1960 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- City of Buffalo - Mayor's Budget Recommendations - Frank A. Sedita, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Dispute- Police and City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Erie County CSEA, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Dispute - Fire Fighters and City of Buffalo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- ILR Voice, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- ILR Voice, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- FOI, 1948-1951 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- FOI, 1951-1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- FOI, 1955-1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- ILR Research Report, 1958-1968 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- ILR Report Card, 1955-1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- The Voice, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- The Voice (Box 19, Folder 2)
- The ILR Student Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Long-Range Planning Task Force, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- ASTD National Vice President, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- A.S.T.D. Board Meeting - Feb. 11-13, 1970 Phoenix, Arizona (Box 19, Folder 6)